adrenalin.com.au 2015-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Adrenalin

**Copyright**  
Copyright in the Material on this Web Site is owned, or licensed by ADRENALINE PTY LTD.  
Except where necessary for viewing, the Material on this web site on your browser, or as permitted under the Copyright Act of 1968, or other applicable laws, no Material on this web site may be reproduced, adapted, uploaded to a third party, linked to, framed, performed in public, distributed, or transmitted in any form by any process without the specific written consent of ADRENALINE PTY LTD.

'Adrenalin', 'LIVE Adrenalin', 'A.365', 'Serious Fun', ‘Corporate Adrenalin’ and ‘a.gear’ all associated trademarks, are trademarks of ADRENALINE PTY LTD.  ACN 117 402 838.  
 ****

**Privacy**

ADRENALINE PTY LTD takes the issue of safeguarding your privacy online seriously. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Adrenalin network of sites (and emails) including [www.adrenalin.com.au](http://www.adrenalin.com.au/) and [www.adrenalin.com.au/corporate/](http://www.adrenalin.com.au/corporate/).

ADRENALINE PTY LTD has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, [www.adrenalin.com.au](http://www.adrenalin.com.au/). TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organisations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, [please contact us](https://www.adrenalin.com.au/contact/). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

**Collection of personal information by Adrenalin**   
The personal information we collect and store will depend on what products and services you request from us. This includes (but is not limited to) information provided when requesting an adventure booking, gift voucher, gear and/or membership. Our sites registration form requests users’ [which includes third party personal information where applicable collected as described below] to give us contact and profile information such as name, email address, phone number, mailing address, age, medical conditions and dietary requirements.  Some of the requested information is required in order to receive the Adrenalin product or service; other information is optional.  
 **  
Where your personal information is stored**   
Where we store your personal information depends on what products and services you have requested from Adrenalin. Data is stored in our CRM for the use of processing transactions, providing order confirmations and dispatching products. Information provided in customer feedback forms is also stored on this system. We also maintain an email database for subscribers to our monthly e-newsletters.  
 **  
Ways we use data**   
We collect your personal information so that we can use it for our functions and services. This may include, but is not limited to:

  * processing your orders including bookings, gift vouchers, gear and membership.
  * providing confirmation of your adventure booking and advise of any changes or additional information.
  * sending out feedback and surveys and addressing any issues or complaints.
  * answering any queries about Adrenalin and its products and services.
  * sending targeted advertising and promotions that allow us to provide our service;
  * sending special deals, promotions and offers based on users interests plus other news on Adrenalin including updates of new, or enhanced services.
  * confirming receipt of profile changes.
  * serving ads, promotions and special offers on Facebook. Any personal information provided to Facebook will be "hashed", a process that summarises text into a short fingerprint that cannot be decrypted and does not allow the original information to be recovered later by decryption. At no time will Facebook have access to any original, discernible personal information that it does not already have.

If you do not provide us with your personal information, we will be unable to do one or more of the above. Upon placing an order with Adrenalin, you are automatically subscribed to receive our monthly e-newsletter and associated communications as per section below on ‘inferred consent’.  
 **  
Inferred consent**   
Section 2.3.2 of the Australian e-Marketing Code of Practise states that  _“Message Originators and Message Service Providers may send…Commercial Communications to Recipients…providing that… it can be reasonably Inferred … that the Recipient has Consented to receive such Commercial Communications (Inferred Consent)._ ” According to section 2.4.1 ‘Inferred consent’ is deemed to exist if Adrenalin can show that the Recipient has an existing and continuing relationship with us, and would have a reasonable expectation of receiving such commercial communications. Recipients therefore include all customers, account holders, subscribers, members, licencees, registered users, employees and contractors. For this reason, every person who submits an order for an Adrenalin product, or service will automatically be added to our subscriber database.  
 **  
Disclosure of data**   
We will not share your information with third parties for their promotional purposes without your permission; however we may obtain personal and other information from you to enable us to provide our services or products to you.   
Personal information may also be disclosed to our third party service providers as described below:

  * To the adventure provider for the purpose of processing your booking request
  * To others in the event of a medical emergency
  * To any entity to which we are required, or authorised by or under law to disclose such information such as, in responding to a formal request in a court order, judicial proceeding or subpoena.
  * To protect against misuse or unauthorised use of Adrenalin
  * To protect the safety, or property of our members, or the public.
  * We use a third party payment processor to fulfill payment for services procured on the Site.
  * We may disclose your information to third parties for the purposes of collecting and publishing your feedback about the Adrenalin buying process.
  * In the event of a sale, merger, or acquisition of some, or all of Adrenalin’s assets, your personal information could likely be a part of the transferred assets. In such an event we shall notify you by a notice on the home page of any information and privacy practices that would change as a result.

Third parties may access and collect information only as required to perform their functions and are not permitted to use the information for their promotional purposes.

These third parties may be located in Australia or overseas, including but not limited to the United States and the United Kingdom.

We request demographic information for our own market research and understanding of our customers. With this information we can provide our users with content we think they might be interested in. Some, but not all, of this information is required to participate in Adrenalin programs, however we believe we will be able to provide users with a better service if demographic information is provided. During the registration process, subscribers may be asked if they would like to have their registration information made available to companies that wish to offer products and services that our subscribers may be interested in. We will never share your information with third parties unless you grant us permission to do so.  
 **  
Collection of information other than personal information**

  * IP addresses/operating system/browser type: When you visit our web site or click on one of our links, we may automatically record information such as your I.P. address, operating system, browser version, date and time of your visit, pages you accessed and information you downloaded. We use this information to generate usage statistics, ensure that our site and emails are accessible to the widest possible audience and to assist in improving the quality and usability of our website. We may also use I.P. addresses to track abuse of our system.
  * Links: When we provide you with links in our emails, they may include a special tracking code unique to you, which allows us to determine which content and advertisements are most popular. We may share this data in aggregate form, but we will never share it in individual form.
  * Cookies: A cookie is a small string of information that a website transfers to your browser for identification purposes. We may use cookies to determine which third party offers our members utilise and to personalise your current visit to our website. The information in cookies is not tied to your personal information. Most internet browsers can be set up to accept, or reject cookies, however rejecting cookies may limit the functionality of our website. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.
  * Web beacons: Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyse how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.
  * Our tracking utility company use both session ID and persistent cookies. The use of cookies by our tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.
  * Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information.
  * We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 of Flash to store preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information.  Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). 
  * We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking Here.  Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.
  * 

**Third-party links**   
This site (and our emails) contain links to other sites. Adrenalin.com.au is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We also provide users with the capacity to share information on the Site on other platforms. These widgets do not store or use your personal information.  
 ****

**Social Media Widgets**   
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Referral Program**   
We may invite you to provide information (such as name and e-mail address) of your friends and family whom you think would like to receive our special offers. The users referred to us receive invitation e-mails, but do not become members until they confirm their interest in our service. We use the third party information you provide to send this one time email. Adrenaline Pty Ltd stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.  Your friend may [contact us](https://www.adrenalin.com.au/contact/) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**E-commerce**   
Our servers are equipped with 128-bit encryption bit technology (designated security keys from authorised certificate-of-trust distributors) for secure purchases and form ordering made within the shopping area. Users’ are notified of encryption processing when a gold padlock appears on the bottom right of the browser. While we take every measure to employ industry accepted security standards, please be aware no security mechanism is 100% secure.

**Unsubscribe**   
If you no longer wish to receive Adrenalin’s publications, you may remove your details from the subscriptions list by clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of the associated email. Alternatively, [please contact us](https://www.adrenalin.com.au/contact/). Please note that by law, Adrenalin has 5 days to action your unsubscribe request.  
 **  
Reviews  
** We provider users’ an opportunity to review their adventures; we post their first name and last initial with their review after obtaining their consent. Please be aware that Adrenalin is not responsible for the personal information a user selects to include within their review. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can [contact us](https://www.adrenalin.com.au/contact/).

**Notification of Changes**   
Adrenalin reserves the right to modify this privacy policy. For this reason, you should regularly check our policy to ensure that you are up to date on our policy. Should we make material changes in the manner we handle your personal information, we shall notify you by a prominent notice on the home page prior to the change becoming effective.  
 **  
Access and Correction of your personal information**   
You can ask to obtain access to your personal information that we hold, although under some circumstances permitted by law, we may not provide such information to you. It is important to us that the personal information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up to date. If you would like your personal information corrected or deleted, [please contact us](https://www.adrenalin.com.au/contact/) with your updated information.  
 **  
Data Retention**   
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, [please contact us](https://www.adrenalin.com.au/contact/). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  
  **  
Contacting the web site or webmaster**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, [please contact us](https://www.adrenalin.com.au/contact/) or call us on 1300 791 793. We will make all reasonable attempts to respond to your enquiry.  
By Mail: 20 Burton, Darlinghurst, NSW 2010 Australia.

Last Modified 10th December 2014.
